Yeah, yeah!
That's good!
Right where I want it!
Good work, Meester.
As long as we keep moving upwards, we
should ward off any further attacks!
Hmph.
Very interesting.
I think I finally understand
how those backstabbing
hooligans managed to
betray the boss and live.
Seko, did you capture their agonized mugs?
You know how much I love
the totally desperate
contortions they make while
fighting for their lives.
Oh, oh!
Yoooo!
But a vis-simile seko!
Hm.
As our curiosity continues to grow, so
too does the boldness of our keen spirits.
And it is the very same inquisitiveness
that fuels our cognitive evolution.
I yearn to see it.
What glorious grimaces will they unveil as
they wrestle with the cold jaws of death?
Ahh!
Hmm.
That's right, I almost forgot.
A little reward for my intrepid cameraman.
How does two sound? Oh!
You want three?
Gracious, three whole treats?
Ah!
Greedy mutt.
All right, three it is.
Are you ready, boy?
Because they're coming at you now!
Yuck!
Oh, whoops, my bad!
psycho, yes, you are! Now go!
I'm counting on you to find
Bucerati and his band of idiots.
Be sure to let them have a
little taste of sanctuary.
I love you,
I love
you
Thank you.
Stay cold
Achimari no Kogelin
Right now,
our number one priority should be making
it to Rome as quickly as possible.
Hey, Giorno, how goes
Narancia's treatment?
Healing him here is going
to be kind of tricky.
His injuries are all teeming
with an aggressive mold.
All right, Mista.
We're clear to ascend.
Let's get to the top of those stairs
and hit the road as fast as we can.
That was cold.
What has gotten into him?
Such a jerk.
He didn't even think to
ask if Narancia was okay.
Also, before that,
when you guys were desperately
struggling to get out of the boat,
remember what he said?
He ordered you to toss the turtle like you
were all just disposable pieces of trash.
What are you so pissed about?
Of course he said that.
I'm the idiot who got on the boat.
I mean, I'm glad we're alive and all,
but don't forget that we nearly
died because of my stupid ass.
Besides,
if Bucciarati hadn't told
me to throw the turtle,
I might have ended up
dropping it in the ocean.
Look, I don't need a lecture.
The only thing I'm trying to say is, he
could stand to be a little nicer to us.
I'll admit, I've never really been that
good at talking about feelings and stuff.
But I'm guessing you wouldn't be so
mad if he just asked if you were okay.
Do I got it right?
Difference between you and me is I
already know how Bucciarati thinks.
but it looks like you're
still trying to figure
out how to get inside
that weird head of his.
Excuse me?
What are you trying to say?
Look, all that matters right now
is getting to Rome in one piece.
You'll have all the time you need
to sort out your feelings later.
I'm not feeling too hot right now.
Let me get some shut-eye.
I know we gotta keep climbing,
but what are we gonna do on the
off chance we have to descend?
It's fine.
This village was built into the mountainside,
meaning the roads are on an incline.
Also, keep in mind there's still
some traffic on the outskirts.
The mold has yet to
spread too far from here.
If we can get to a vehicle and
leave immediately, we'll be fine.
We must stay focused on Rome.
So, which car should we take?
The one next to the dead body.
With any luck, we just might be able
to find the key to the ignition on him.
Startled by a mere hand
decaying from the mold.
I'll keep a watch on our rear, while you
sprint to the car as quickly as you can.
Right.
Mister, hold on. Just now.
I felt something. Get a move on. Got it!
Don't just stand there and gawk!
Hurry and climb those stairs like I said!
That's what I'm trying to do, Buterati!
Oh, shit!
We're starting to sink!
It's sliding off of the wall!
What the?
At this rate, the ground's gonna
smalow this whole damn staircase.
This has to be the work of another stand.
Our mold user has a friend.
Screw me sideways.
If we keep sinking, this mold's gonna
melt our asses down into puddles of crap.
We're gonna have to jump.
Hey, my gun!
It's not sinking.
The entire staircase itself is
dissolving right into the ground!
What the hell?
It's them!
They're rushing toward a
location from beneath the ground!
Mista, get on the wall now!
Go, Zipperman!
To counter me this fast, not bad.
But there's something else to their power.
The ground feels oddly hard to
the touch, even through my stand.
Yet I continue to sink in spite
of its solidity. Meanwhile,
my opponent can freely move around
beneath me as if the stairs were liquid.
Merda!
I've no way of finding them!
It's a total guessing game!
Get the crap out of your
damn ears, six bullets!
Come back to Papa!
Yee-haw!
A flesh-eating fungus, and
now a subterranean predator.
Both of them deftly working
together in tandem to take us down.
I'll admit I'm impressed.
A flawless duo.
We've yet to encounter
such a pair of killers.
Well, maybe these violent little assholes
should hurry up and get married already.
You were right on the money.
Our decaying friend over there
still got the key to his ride.
Strunzo!
I swear I saw him pop out just now.
The goddamn coward just dove
from the stairs to the wall.
Damn, what now?
Run away, quickly!
God damn it!
Even if we make it to
the car in one piece,
we won't have enough
time to start the engine!
I'll stop this guy dead in his tracks!
You go on ahead!
Don't stop running!
The ground is still in its solid state!
Your bullets will ricochet!
If this quicksand shit's gonna
stay hard like normal ground,
I'll just have to get him when
he tries to pull me under.
This guy likes to hit hard from up close.
I bet his range sucks.
I should be able to see him
the second he tries to get me.
Then it's murder time, baby!
There!
I knew you couldn't stay away!
Now, eat this!
No, mister!
Of freakin' course.
I should've guessed a close
range power base stand
would have some way to defend
itself against bullets.
Although, you're not the only
one who knows that trick.
My little buddies can deflect bullets too!
Those first three shots should...
Oh, come on!
What is he saving me
for later he must think
i've become an easy target
now that i'm wounded?
Hurry and pick up the key
Buchananthi start the engine!
What the hell man get inside the damn car
if we're able to drive
out of this village!
We'll be fine just as long as
we all keep heading to Rome.
Where is that guy running off to now?
Ow!
Wait, what?
So, you're tracking our movements
from beneath the earth, huh?
Quite a terrifying power.
But, what is your extent?
Can you really discern my true intentions?
It seems not even you
possess that ability.
I can see it on your face.
THE FACE COUNCIL
Arab Nelchi!
My...
My face!
Huh?
What is it?
Hey, Cioccolata!
Three days ago, you heard the news, right?
You know the stand that the boss put
on the airplane thingy? Yeah, yeah!
Notorious Chase is what I
think I heard it was called!
Now Seko, aren't you supposed to be busy
hunting down those bastards like I asked?
Don't waste time chatting.
Cioccolata, please!
This is important, very important!
Notorious Chase!
Is it a living stand, or
is it a dead stand? Hmm?
Why are you asking all of a sudden?
I know it sounds like a stupid question,
Please answer me!
Let's say that Notorious Chase
were here right now with us.
You think your mold would be
able to grow on him at all?
Like, do you know if it would
be able to grow on a dead stand?
Notorious Chase, huh?
Isn't that the one whose user was filled
with so much vengeance and hatred,
his stand found a way to live
on even after he was killed?
Who knows?
I confess I'm kind of curious myself,
but I don't have the foggiest idea.
What I do know is that
green tea will putrefy
any living organism it
comes into contact with.
So the mold won't grow on rocks and
other non-alive stuff, is that right?
Forget this!
I asked you to film those
fools with their death row,
so stop dawdling and hop to it!
Yeah, but that's the thing, Cioccolata!
Take a gander at the hill!
Up there! On the road! Huh?
Hey Seko, why am I watching
a car leave the village?
Oh, don't tell me the passengers
are who I think they are!
Why are you letting them get away?
I don't know! I don't know!
It all happened so fast!
He actually hit me right in my face!
That Burjarati guy!
There wasn't any mold
on him, not even a bit!
And I even watched him jump down!
HE SHOULDN'T HAVE BEEN ABLE TO
ATTACK ME FROM WHERE HE WAS!
AAAAAAAH!
THERE'S NO WAY IT COULD
HAVE BEEN POSSIBLE!
HIS BODY MUST SOMEHOW
BE RESISTED TO THE MOLD!
HOW IS THIS EVEN HAPPENING?!
I HAVEN'T THE SLIGHTEST.
You, uh...
you had me fooled for a sec there.
I actually thought you'd
plunge to your own death.
You scared the crap out of me.
Was it zippers you used to
cling onto the wall like that?
It must have been close.
Looks like you didn't get
an ounce of mold on you.
Hey, Mista, you should get some rest.
I closed your wounds, but they
could start bleeding again.
You just sit back and let me keep a
lookout for any cars that are on our tail.
Yeah.
Bucciarati, your wrist is injured.
It looks pretty bad from here.
Let me patch you up.
Hey, Bucciarati, are you listening?
There's a chance the mold
has infected your wound.
Please let me see it.
What are you...
Wait, what the hell?
There's no warmth on his skin.
And his pulses.
Jonah, what's wrong?
You seem a little perturbed.
Did you say something?
Did that really just happen?
So it wasn't just my imagination.
This is exactly like that
other time in Venice.
I thought he was acting strange back
then, but I'd written it off as nothing.
I suppose I was careless, but perhaps
I've realized this just a second too late.
I'm quickly losing all feeling.
No, I haven't had my sense of
touch for quite a while now.
So, Yer, then that means when you rescued
Trish from the boss back in Venice...
Uchirati, you can't
really be saying you're...
It's strange.
I'd already come to
accept this as destiny.
I thought of it as a little gift
handed down to me from heaven above.
The life force you gave my
wounded body could not save me,
even though I'm certain
you intended it to.
Unfortunately, all it has
done is delay the inevitable.
But why?
Why'd you have to keep this from us?
Back then,
Golden Wind was perfectly able to heal
all your injuries without a problem.
I know that it can do it again.
There's no reason it can't
fix whatever's wrong with you.
Giorno, I know this is hard.
But even your Golden Wind
understands this truth
much better than anyone
else I would expect.
Nothing can free a person
from Death's stubborn grasp.
By the time you'd reached
me, it was too late.
Death has me now.
I trust you will keep
this matter between us.
Damn it, Bucciarati!
You can't just ask me to accept this!
I'm not gonna let...
Wait, Jonah, quiet!
Listen, can you hear it too?
Or is it just me?
I don't see any other cars.
Use your ears then.
This thing's coming in hot.
What the...
Up above, it's a helicopter!
He's raining mold down on us!
What the hell is going on?! Put it up!
Slow the hell down!
This road goes downhill!
We'll trigger the mold!
Juno! Masa!
We're abandoning ship!
Hold on tight!
Keep climbing!
Get as far up as you possibly can!
The subconscious.
That's what stands are meant to reflect.
They're supposed to
mirror their users' minds
if there's even a trace
of guilt in their hearts.
The user may subconsciously
stop themselves at some point,
but this Katsune he revels in carnage!
It's all he lives for his
stand is cruelty incarnate.
What a heartless monster
there are no brakes
on that freak train hey
stay with me now, honey?
Don't worry Papa. We'll get a doctor.
Wait stop it. You idiot.
Don't go down the hill I have
to go get a doctor for my job!
Yo, what's going on there?
You see that?
This damn mold.
It's spreading like fire.
Despicable.
Rome's population is in the millions.
It completely dwarfs that fishing village.
Not to mention it's home
to some of the boss's men.
He would suffer collateral damage.
This Thronzo doesn't even care.
He's just having the time of his life!
At this rate, he's gonna
wipe out all of Rome!
And what's to stop him from
moving on to the next big city?
Our troubles don't end there!
In the event that we fail to make haste,
the mode is almost sure to outrun us!
It'll cut through the Coliseum
long before we can get to it!
Mista!
Can you tell if that helicopter
is within your range?
Your answer better be yes, cause
it's our only path forward!
Bring this bastard back down to Earth!
Hear that, fellas?
Showtime!
One-downed helicopter coming right up!
Yee-haw!
The chopper was the diversion.
Are you kidding me with this?
That's one hell of a tactic.
A flying hunk of metal to cover
the ground-melting weirdo.
Good.
Seko has landed safely.
Or should I say submerged.
Either way, those morons
have no means of escape.
Admittedly, the weather is quite lovely
for a blind date at the Coliseum.
It's a shame that Green Tea
and I will have to rain on it.
Damn it!
He's gonna close in on us soon!
And falling back downhill's not an option!
Mista, focus on the helicopter!
We cannot allow him to escape!
That bastard will fall by my hand!
I hate to break it to you, but
your hands ain't gonna reach him!
I can't light up a proper shot for
his tank or propellers from here!
Not so fast.
You can't know for sure until you try.
I told you, it's too far.
Trust me when I say I know the extent of
my bullets range better than anyone else.
See what I mean?
He got away!
Now that homicidal badger's here!
We just landed a direct hit, Mista.
Now you and I are gonna
go take down that pilot.
Let's get moving!
Wait, you can't mean, on foot?
Shit!
How did...
We have to exterminate the mold before
it has a chance to reach the Coliseum.
Bucciarati.
Our underground friend.
I'm leaving him to you.
Get going, ragazzi!
I'll take care of this one!
Stand up, join us.
Come on, just see us alive!
We are the power.
Who'll see the future?
Cause we are the fighters.
Just fighting for Christ.
We'll
be
right back.
Thank
you.